[Music]
[Música]
Well there are a lot of people asking me
y Bueno hay mucha gente preguntándome
about the Willy thing come on I'm going to
por el tema de Willy venga va lo voy a
look at it really fast I'm going to look at it
mirar rapidísimo lo voy a mirar
really fast okay the last song of the day
rapidísimo vale el último tema del día
today come on you can't complain we've been
hoy vamos no os podéis quejar llevamos 4
live for 4 and a half hours almost the only thing
horas y media de directo casi lo único
that I'm going to ask of all of you okay And I
que sí os voy a pedir a todos vale Y ya
'm done
estoy
eh let's go I think I have the right to
eh vamos me creo con el derecho de
ask you whatever the hell I'm not going to
pediros lo que me dé la gana noos voy a
ask you for members because I know that there are
pedir miembros porque yo sé que hay
a lot of people who can't give members or
mucha gente que no puede dar miembros ni
become members even though it's only worth 90
hacerse miembro aunque solamente vale 90
cents whoever can do it But what I am
céntimos el que pueda que haga Pero lo
going to require of all of you who
que sí os voy a exigir a todos los que
are watching the live right now is
estéis viendo ahora mismo el directo es
that I checked that you are subscribed and the
que revisé que estéis suscritos y el
like there are a lot of people here there are a lot of
like hay aquí mucha gente hay mucha
people who can give like and
gente que le puede dar a like y a
subscribe So go see I'm going to
suscribirse Así que dle a ver me voy a
find out about this [ __ ] I don't know what it's about
enterar de esta movida no sé de lo que
says IB exposes that greev and Willy
va dice IB expone que greev y Willy le
asked him to do this to fight at the evening I
pidieron esto para pelear en la velada O
mean if it isn't Cliff Bay who is
sea si no es cliff Bay que nos está
putting the youtube gossip on us here about
metiendo aquí el chisme youtubero de lo
what  this move is about It's that they would have
que trata esta movida Es que le habrían
set conditions for him to accept that
puesto condiciones para sí aceptar
fight at the evening of the
ese ese combate pelea en la velada del
year It turns out that the same I did a
año Resulta ser que el mismo I hizo un
live where he was with the shas and
directo en donde estaba con el shas y
mentioned the following right that Thank you
mencionó lo siguiente verdad que Gracias
Now there has been a certain between quotes
Ahora habido una cierta entre comillas
well that kind of dispute again that has been
bueno esa medio disputa otra vez que se
reopened that if I such And that no and that I don't
ha reabierto que si yo tal Y que no y
know how many But before
que no sé cuántos Pero antes de que
the subject of Willy
pasara el tema de que otra vez Willy
greev talking about the subject again happened, I
greev volviesen a hablar del tema yo les
proposed to Willy Rex and Gref that we fight at
propuse a Willy Rex y a gref pelear en
the Delman evening a big kiss
la velada delman un beso muchísimo
Thank you man okay I proposed it to both of them
Gracias tío vale se lo propuse a los dos
many months ago because the evening
hace hace muchos meses porque la velada
of year 3 was in July and it was for the
del año 3 fue en julio y fue para la
evening of year 3 So this must be
velada del año 3 Así que esto debe ser
in January 2023 December 2022 I
en enero de 2023 diciembre de 2022 se lo
proposed it to both okay So here it
propuse a los dos vale Así que aquí
could be aiming high the ibay eh
puede ser aspirando alto el ibay eh
either of the two I don't want to say the
cualquiera de los dos no quiero decir el
name okay because in the end there are people
nombre vale porque al final hay gente
who will think that it could be gref because of the
que se pensará que puede ser gref por la
closeness that I have with him but the
cercanía que tengo con él pero la
reality is that I  I proposed
realidad es que yo se lo propuse a los
both greev and Willy okay and the
dos tanto a greev como a Willy vale y la
reality that this fight didn't happen or
realidad de que esta pelea no se diese o
well I'm going to leave it a large part of the
bueno voy a dejarlo en gran parte de la
blame that this fight didn't happen is
culpa de que esta pelea no se diese es
that one of the two asked me for a million
que uno de los dos me pidió un millón de
euros to participate a million euros let's
euros para participar un millón de euros
see if it's true of course Let's see I'll
a ver sí que es verdad claro A ver os
tell you one thing and it's not a joke Oh
digo una cosa y no es ninguna fumada Oh
the live restarted eh Surely it
se reinició el directo eh Seguramente se
fell no Let's see I'll tell you one thing and it's not
caído no A ver os digo una cosa y no es
a joke and it's going to generate
una fumada y va en la velada genera
several million Of course if you're going to
varios millones Claro si tú me vas a
put me a fight between greev and Willy Rex if
poner una pelea de greev y Willy Rex si
you're going to put me a fight between greev and
tú me vas a poner una pelea de greev y
Willy Rex What are the chances What
Willy Rex Qué posibilidades hay Qué
chances do you think there are that because of
posibilidades creéis que hay de que por
that fight Twitch will increase
esa pelea por esa pelea se aumente
Twitch itself will move so
Twitch el propio Twitch se mueva para
that it can support the millions of
que se aguanten los millones de
viewers that are needed okay the
espectadores que haga falta vale las
brands pay more everything everything will
marcas paguen más todo todo se
multiply more and now you tell me is it worth
multiplique más y ahora tú me dices vale
the million or not worth the million man
el millón o no vale el millón hombre
who asked for the million Javi Put a
quién pidió el millón Javi Pon una
survey it's that they are two people
encuesta es que son dos personas
eh They are two people that and this
eh Son dos personas que y esto lo habré
I'll talk to someone really big, I'm not going to
yo con con alguien muy grande no os voy
give you the name in case he gets
a dar el nombre por si acaso se
upset. But anyway, he's one
molestase Pero bueno es un youtuber
of the biggest youtubers and streamers out there and
streamer de los más grandes que hay y
talking about the subject of the
hablando sobre el tema de del podcast de
Delo podcast, he told me because I thought so, that
delo me dijo porque yo pensaba que sí
Gref would be willing to gossip and
que gre estaría dispuesto al salseo y
all that and moreover, yes, yes, for whatever reason, it
demás y más además si si por lo que sea
could be an offer that, by the
se le pudiera ser una oferta que por
way, Delos denied that he was
cierto delos me desmintió que que se
paid in the podcast, eh, there are a lot of
cobrase en el podca eh que hay mucha
people who claim that in the podcast everyone gets
gente que afirma que en el podca todos
paid I don't know what and everyone doesn't get paid, okay,
cobran no sé qué y todos no cobran vale
eh, The Thing Is What He Told Me Is That Gref,
eh La Movida Es que me dijo Es que gref
if he does something, it's not for money because he
si hace algo no es por dinero porque es
already has a lot, the bastard. I mean, no, no, no, no, there's
que ya tiene mucho el cabrón O sea no no
not going to be an amount of
no te no no va a haber una cantidad de
money that surprises him, there has to be a
dinero que le sorprenda tiene que ser un
bit of context. Javi, this about eb. There were
poco de contexto Javi esto de eb Eran
three stories and two were false and one was
tres historias y dos eran falsas y uno
real. Gre reacted to this and said that it
real gre reaccionó a esto y dijo que no
wasn't real or that at least he didn't remember
era real o que al menos no recordaba
saying it himself. Oh, I mean, you got ahead of me, to the
decirlo él Ah o sea te me has adelantado
clip by, no, you got ahead of me, to the by,
al al clip by no te me adelantaste al by
no. Greetings, Javi, Thank you.  for always
no Saludos Javi Gracias por siempre
bringing the best content and always in the
traer el mejor contenido y siempre de la
best way kiss a hug it is
mejor forma beso un abrazo se agradece
very much appreciated after 4 hours of
muchísimo ya después de 4 horas de
live those words a handsome kiss I
directo esas palabras un beso guapo me
curse my [ __ ] mother Okay so
cago en mi [__] madre Vale entonces
obviously I don't know if having reached
obviamente no sé si yo al haber llegado
that figure this would have happened because there
a esa cifra esto se hubiese dado porque
was some more step but one of the
quedaba algún paso más pero uno de los
two asked me for a million euros and he
dos a mí me pidió un millón de euros y
was the main culprit or the main
fue el El Gran culpable o el gran
cause of this not happening So
causante de que esto no se diese Así que
told [ __ ] very expensive Willy eh the
contadas [__] muy caro Willy eh la
truth is I Of course if you pay a
verdad yo Claro que si tú le pagas un
million euros to only one you had to
millón de euros a uno solo tenías que
pay the other too or what Or you pay
pagar al otro también o qué O le pagas a
one because who of the two has more
uno porque quién de los dos tienen más
caches than the other at the moment
caches que el otro en estos momentos
but apart from that I tell you that let's
pero es que aparte es que os digo que a
see it depends on who it is yes they could ask for that
ver depende quién sea sí podría pedir
eh I mean obviously those who have
eso eh o sea evidentemente los que ha
brought it can't ask for a million
llevado no lo pueden pedir un millón
okay those who have brought those who have
vale los que han llevado los que han
been the participants of the vada this
sido los participantes de la vada este
year can't ask for 1 kilo okay but of
año no pueden pedir 1 kilo vale pero
course you take me Willy Rex
claro es que tú me llevas a Willy Rex a
Willy Rex and Gref if in itself the
Willy Rex y a gref si ya de por sí la
evening generates a few of  millions
velada genera unos cuantos de millones
the evening generates a few
la velada genera unos cuantos de
millions we were doing some
millones estuvimos haciendo unos
calculations barely knowing But
cálculos apenas sin saber Pero
simply with the
simplemente con la con la venta de
ticket sales I won't say anything just telling these
entradas no diré nada contadas estas
three anecdotes so people can give their opinion Which
tres anécdotas que la gente opine Cuál
is the real one Which are the two real ones
es la real Cuáles son las dos reales
sorry and which is the fake one however there is
perdón y cuál es La falsa sin embargo
a reality to all of this and gref
hay una realidad de todo esto y gref
reacted to this same thing it was me damn I don't
reaccionó a esto mismo fui yo ostras no
remember eh I don't think I asked for a
me acuerdo eh No creo que yo pidiera un
million euros to participate like you
millón de euros para participar en plan
have to give me a million with I don't
me tienes que dar un millón con no
participate I mean it's okay to earn money
participo O sea está bien ganar dinero
if you do a fight but a million Hey I
si haces un combate pero un millón Oye
think this is fake news No this is
esto creo que son fake news No esto son
fake news from but but but but to
fake news de i pero pero pero pero para
stir up gossip and I make a thread about
armar salseo y que le haga un hilo a
Willy on Twitter and he makes another one and we
Willy en Twitter y él me haga otro y nos
hit each other with our fists what the [ __ ] I mean
peguemos A puñetazos qué [__] O sea a
Willy on Twitter from but but but but
Willy en Twitter de pero pero pero pero
to stir up gossip and I make a thread about
para armar salseo y que le haga un hilo
Willy on Twitter and he makes another
a Willy en Twitter y él me haga otro
one and we hit each other with our fists what the
otro y nos peguemos A puñetazos qué
[ __ ] I mean I can't imagine saying it's
[__] o sea yo no me imagino diciendo
true that I  I have a weird memory but I
es verdad que yo tengo memoria rara pero
can't imagine saying Give me a million
no me imagino diciendo Dame un millón
to fight Willy Rex and I also can't
para pelear contra Willy Rex y tampoco
imagine Willy Rex saying I'll
me imagino a Willy Rex diciendo I por un
do it for a million, okay, okay, be careful eh
millón lo hago bueno bueno cuidado eh
Willy Willy has his life
que a Willy Willy tiene la vida
sorted but a little bit of money doesn't
solucionada pero un poco de panoja no le
interest him but a lot of money, be
interesa pero un montón de panoja
careful eh it calls anyone, anyone
cuidado eh a cualquiera a cualquiera le
okay, I think these people don't care about
llama vale yo creo que a esta gente no
having a kilo more or
le les da igual tener un kilo más que
less dude in the bank no, I think
menos tío en el banco no yo creo que
these people are just
esta gente ya lo que están haciendo es
doing things that they
Ya por gusto hacer las cosas que le
like for fun eh I mean these people have
gusten eh o sea esta gente tienen
quite a few millions eh most of
bastantes millones eh la mayoría de
them have a few million
ellos tienen unos cuantos de millones de
look here there are a lot of millions of
mira aquí hay un montón de millones de
euros whatever These people already do what they
euros sea Esta gente ya lo que hace lo
like and they're going to be
hacen ya por gusto y van a estar
doing it for fun continuing to earn
haciéndolo por gusto siguiendo ganando
lots of money until this is over
muchísima pasta hasta que esto se acabe
Okay and life is super sorted dude
Vale y la vida super resueltas tío de
for
por
life then obviously I don't know if I looked at
vida entonces obviamente no s si yo mir
the face of the
la cara del
crash it's what a tremendous son of a
choca es que tremendo hijo de la gran
[ __ ] in his new house it's worth 6 million
[__] en su casa nueva esta de 6 millones
euros Having reached that figure
de euros Al haber llegado a esa cifra
this would have happened because there was
esto se hubiese dado porque quedaba
some  one more step but one of the two
algún paso más pero uno de los dos a mí
asked me for a million euros and he was the one who was the
me pidió un millón de euros y fue el El
main culprit or the main cause of
Gran culpable o el gran causante de que
this not happening this is incredible nothing
esto no se diese esto es increíble nada
from the year TR Hey but guys do you
del año TR Oye pero chicos vosotros
think that if this were true I
pensáis que si esto fuera verdad os lo
tell you sincerely IB would not have
digo sinceramente IB no lo hubiera
told it before, I mean the fight has been talked about so many
contado antes o sea se ha hablado tantas
times Gref vs. Willy
veces de El Combate gref contra Willy
Willy vs. Greev that Ibai is going to come
Willy contra greev que va a venir ibai
a year later and say that it didn't happen
un año después a decir que no se hizo
because one of them asked for a million euros It
porque uno pidió un millón de euros Me
seems very strange to me I mean I don't think I would
parece muy raro O sea no creo que yo
say this and you'll say But Gref how could
dijera esto y diréis Pero gref cómo no
you not know if I know dude I mean it's
lo vas a saber si yo que sé tío o sea es
not to put my hand on it but I don't think I
por no poner la mano pero yo creo que no
said that anywhere and I can't imagine
dije eso en ningú y tampoco me imagino a
well it's that I don't know maybe it
bueno es que no lo sé a lo mejor
's Willab F July and it was for the evening
se willab F julio y fue para la velada
of the year 3 So this must be is that let's
del año 3 Así que esto debe sea es que a
see you don't have to give me a million
ver a mí no me tienes que dar un millón
euros to fight Willy Rex you
de euros para pelear contra Willy Rex a
give me 900000 and it will probably go the
mí me das 900000 y probablemente vaya
same n this is a lie guys fake news
igual n esto es mentira chicos fake news
fake fake fake news  fake news guys
fake fake fake news fake news chicos
invented by the noble giant is telling me three
inventada del gigante noble me está tres
stories one is fake How Wait
historias una es fake Cómo Espérate
Wait he has told three stories
Espérate que ha contado tres historias
referring to the fight and he said that one
referentes al combate y ha dicho que una
is fake And that is one of them ha Ah he
es fake Y esa es una de ellas ha Ah me
bit me he did that the [ __ ] Sure
mordido ha hecho eso el [__] Claro
but then it doesn't make sense to
pero entonces no tiene sentido
react to a clip I have to
reaccionar a un clip tengo que
react to all three he ate it
reaccionar a los tres se lo ha comido
just like us eh he ate it
igual que nosotros eh se la ha comido
just like us I mean It turns out it
igual que nosotros o sea Resulta ser que
was a game with the chocas in which he
era un juego con el chocas en el que
counted three
contaba tres
one of them was real you would have to
una de ellas era real habría que
listen to the other two that I'm not going to
escuchar las otras dos que no lo voy a
do to know which one was real but
hacer para saber cuál era la real pero
this one certainly
esta desde luego
[Music]
[Música]
no
no